<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Juanjo Llanos</title><link>https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Juanjo Llanos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TwinShop</title><link>https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/twinshop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/twinshop/</guid><description>Summary Link to heading Twinshop is a project I made for the Universidad de Chile which consisted in a web application that shows realtime information about manufacturing machines and allows to generate reports about energy consumption and working time. This app was part of an investigation and development project for the IMA (Advanced Manufacturing Engineering).
Tech Stack Link to heading Flutter 3 Firebase Extended description Link to heading Twinshop was an adaptative and responsive web application that involved communication with Firebase services and external APIs.</description></item><item><title>Registro Clínico Electronico</title><link>https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/rce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ukarus.github.io/en/projects/rce/</guid><description>Summary Link to heading Registro Clínico Electronico (abbreviated as RCE) is a big project made for the Hospital San Juan de Dios and it involved a web application and many integrations with external services and other internal apps. This applicaton allowed doctors and specialists to save medical records, manage their calendar and search for relevant health information about their patients.
Tech Stack Link to heading Laravel 7 Vue.js 2.6 MariaDB Phpunit CKEditor Extended Description Link to heading RCE was one of the most used applications by doctors in the Hospital, it had many useful functionalities for them and it was also used by other staff members who need to manage the calendar and schedule patients appointments.</description></item></channel></rss>